Institute for First Amendment Studies Records MS074
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Audiocassettes, 1980 -- 1999; 1993 -- 1998; MS074.003; 2.2 Linear Feet; 17 Audiovisual Object(s)
  Included in the collection are tapes of talks and speeches made by members of the Religious Right documenting the movements goals and concerns, which were collected by the Institute for First Amendment Studies. Also included are tapes of radio broadcasts in which IFAS founder Skipp Porteous discussed the Religious Right, sometimes in conjunction with representatives of conservative religious organizations. Most of the tapes in this series were produced between 1993 and 1998, although many date back to 1986-1988.
  This series includes a large number of taped talks from the Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conferences from 1993, 1994, 1995, 1996, and 1998, and many from the Reclaiming America Conference held in 1994. Other groups represented in this collection include Concerned Women for America, Focus on Family, and the Council for National Policy. Of these tapes, 394 were numbered and indexed; this order has been maintained.
  The remaining tapes have been sorted by the conference at which the material was created, or by the group responsible for their production, as applicable. Tapes in special, off-sized packaging and the microcassettes are grouped at the end of the series.
  This series is arranged numerically according to index; unnumbered tapes are arranged by organization (where applicable).
  - "Resisting the new world order," Elliott Abrams & Alan Keyes, 1994; MS074.003.005.00001 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 1. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994.
  - "U.S. foreign policy & the new world order," Elliott Abrams & Alan Keyes, 1994; MS074.003.005.00002 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 2. From the Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994.
  - Dr. William Bellavia: AIDs, NYers for Constitutional Freedoms lobby day, 1993-03-09; MS074.003.005.00003 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 3
  - "Listening to America," Speaker: Lamar Alexander, 1994; MS074.003.005.00004 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 4. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994.
  - "Religious liberty: a history of an American invention: by Robert S. Alley, MS074.003.005.00005 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 5. From 46th National Conference on Church and State; Americans United for Separation of Church and State.
  - Alphaphonics, 1994; MS074.003.005.00006 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 6
  - American Justice Federation, Winter, 1994; MS074.003.005.00007 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 7
  - ACTV: Senator William Armstrong, MS074.003.005.00008 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 8
  - "Rhetoric & values: communicating the pro-family message," Tom Atwood & Guy Rodgers, 1993; MS074.003.005.00009 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 9. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993.
  - "America's Godly heritage," speaker: David Barton, 1993; MS074.003.005.00010 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 10. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993.
  - "America's Godly heritage," speaker: David Barton, 1994; MS074.003.005.00011 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 11. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994.
  - "Turning our hearts toward home," speaker: Gary Bauer, 1993; MS074.003.005.00012 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 12. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - "The Washington battle," speaker: Dr. Gary Bauer, 1994; MS074.003.005.00013 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 13. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994.
  - Gary Bauer: what happened in America?, 1994; MS074.003.005.00014 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 14. From Reclaiming America Conference, 1994
  - Flip & aduocaat; Aduocaat & Reed, MS074.003.005.00015 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 15. Title in index: Benham, Flip
  - Barbara Chauney; Bookshop & Flip, MS074.003.005.00016 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 16. Title in index: "Benham, Flip and Barbara."
  - "Turning the tide of America's cultural decline," speaker: Dr. William Bennett, 1993; MS074.003.005.00017 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 17. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - "The politics of virtue," speaker: William Bennett, 1994; MS074.003.005.00018 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 18. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - Choosing your literature for teaching American Christian history, 1994; MS074.003.005.00019 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 19
  - Outcome based education, Sam Blumenfield, MS074.003.005.00020 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 20
  - "Riding the information highway," Jerry Bowyer & Dan Becker, 1994; MS074.003.005.00021 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 21. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - "The family & the workplace," Marshall Breger & Patrick Fagan, 1993; MS074.003.005.00022 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 23. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - "Conservatives & middle Ameica," speaker: Pat Buchanan, 1993; MS074.003.005.00023 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 24. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - Culture wars, Pat Buchanan, Duke University, 1992-04-28; MS074.003.005.00024 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 25
  - "Clintonomics & the coming economic earthquake," speaker: Larry Burkett, 1993; MS074.003.005.00025 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 26. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - Current stats / vital information, Dr. Paul Cameron, Colorado Family Values, 1994-05-16; MS074.003.005.00026 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 27
  - "Lobbying elected officials," Sally Campbell & Heidi Scanlon, 1994; MS074.003.005.00027 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 28. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - CAS Tape #1 copy #1, MS074.003.005.00028 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 29
  - CAS tape #2 copy #1, MS074.003.005.00029 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 30
  - "Remaining pro-life in the realm of politics," speaker: Gov. Robert Casey, 1994; MS074.003.005.00030 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 31. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - "Former Secretary of Defense," speaker: Hon. Dick Cheney, 1994; MS074.003.005.00031 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 32. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - ACTV: Congressman Bill Cobey: "Basic fund raising" and "How to relate to the press," n.d., MS074.003.005.00032 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 33
  - "The Woodstock generation: understanding the Sixties", 1994; MS074.003.005.00033 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 34. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - Tim Collins, Focus on the Family, 1990-07-11; MS074.003.005.00034 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 35
  - CFV - Media, MS074.003.005.00035 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 36
  - "Grassroots" CFV, MS074.003.005.00036 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 37
  - "Chapter leader briefing," Roberta Combs & Alice Patterson, 1994; MS074.003.005.00037 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 38. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - Jerry Cammarata Children of the rainbow curriculum, NYers for Constitutional Freedoms, MS074.003.005.00038 (Box 5)
    IFAS tape 39
  - "Lobbying and political involvement," speaker: Douglas Cook, 1993; MS074.003.006.00001 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 40. From Constitutional Litigation, 3rd Annual Conference, 1993
  - Teaching our theological roots: The historical foundation of our faith, 1994; MS074.003.006.00002 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 41
  - "Why We Need a Balanced Budget," Rep. Delay, Jim Miller & St. Rep. Byrd, 1993; MS074.003.006.00003 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 42. From the Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993.
  - "Getting involved in the Republican Party," Ione Dilley, Leigh Ann Metzger & Pat McSweeny, 1994; MS074.003.006.00004 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 43. From the Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994.
  - "Senate Minority Leader's report," Speaker: Sen. Bob Dole, 1993; MS074.003.006.00005 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 44. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - "Personal testimony," Speaker: Elizabeth Dole, 1994; MS074.003.006.00006 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 45. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - "The Military under siege," Elaine Donnelly & Maj. Melissa Wells-Petry, 1993; MS074.003.006.00007 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 46. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - ACTV: Congressman Bob Dornan, "Conservative wave of the future", MS074.003.006.00008 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 47
  - "Master of ceremonies," speaker: Hon. Bob Dornan, 1994; MS074.003.006.00009 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 48. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - "The politics of race & sex in America," speaker: Dinesh D'Souza, 1993; MS074.003.006.00010 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 49. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - "Discrimination laws and the church," speaker: Richard Duncan, 1993; MS074.003.006.00011 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 50. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - "Building effective precinct organizations," Marlene Elwell & Roberta Combs, 1993; MS074.003.006.00012 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 51. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - Jim Evans: County chapters, NYers for Constitutional Freedoms, 1993-03-09; MS074.003.006.00013 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 52
  - NYCF lobby con - Jim Evans, 1993-03-09; MS074.003.006.00014 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape [53]. Numbered 52 on tape; 53 per index.
  - Falwell NPR, leaving politics, 1986-10-11; MS074.003.006.00015 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 54
  - "America's greatest days are still ahead," speaker: Mike Farris, 1994; MS074.003.006.00016 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 55. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - "Who's afraid of religious conservatives?" speaker: Don Feder, 1994; MS074.003.006.00017 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 56. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - "Why Jewish conservatives are working with Christians," Don Feder & Rabbi Daniel Lapin, 1993; MS074.003.006.00018 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 57. From Christian Coalition Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - "Defending free Speech & the First Amendment," Keith Fournier & Jay Sekulow, 1993; MS074.003.006.00019 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 58. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - [Side A:] FW Mar-June Vol. 9 - 2 & 3; [Side B:] Jan/Feb FW/ Walk Away Win, 1992; MS074.003.006.00020 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 59
  - [Side A:] Walk Away Winter, Freedom Writer, Jan., Feb. Cont.; [Side B:] Cont. Freedom Writer, Feb., March, 1994; MS074.003.006.00021 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 60
  - Tape 2, FGBINFI delegates meeting, One Side - Side A, 1994-07-08; MS074.003.006.00023 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 61
  - "Voter guides: educating pro-family voters," Pat Gartland & Rick Schenker, 1994; MS074.003.006.00024 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 62. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - "Renewing American civilization," speaker: Rep. Newt Gingrich, 1993; MS074.003.006.00025 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 63. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - American Coalition for Traditional Values, Congressman Newt Gingrich, "The window of opportunity", MS074.003.006.00026 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 64
  - "Churches and civic involvement: do's and don'ts," Tom Grabinski & Rev. Richard Overgard, 1994; MS074.003.006.00027 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 65. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - "Family economy: yours & America's," speaker: Sen. Phil Gramm, 1993; MS074.003.006.00028 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 66. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - "Fighting for family friendly health care reform," speaker: Sen Phil Gramm, 1994; MS074.003.006.00029 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 67. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - George Grant, "Biblical principles of political action", 1991; MS074.003.006.00030 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 68. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1991
  - George Grant, Why Christians hate politics, 1994; MS074.003.006.00031 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 69. From Reclaiming America Conference, 1994
  - George Grant, Why liberals win, 1994; MS074.003.006.00032 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 70. From Reclaiming America Conference, 1994
  - "Modern church-state conflicts: have the issues really changed in 40 years?" by Steven K. Green, MS074.003.006.00033 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 71. 46th National Conference on Church and State, Americans United for Separation fo Church and State
  - "1994 voter education kick-off," D.J. Gribbin & Chuck Cunningham, MS074.003.006.00034 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 72. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - "Organizing your neighborhood," D.J. Gribbin & Roberta Combs, 1994; MS074.003.006.00035 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 73. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - "Getting involved in the Democratic Party," Cathe Halford & Beverly Clark, 1994; MS074.003.006.00036 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 74. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - "Bible Prophecy & the doom of America!" (Pastors Riley & Hall), MS074.003.006.00037 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 75
  - "Trumpets of glory: time of the end!" (A gift of love), MS074.003.006.00038 (Box 6)
    IFAS tape 76
  - Jonathan Henry, Cosmic catastrophes and the Big Bang, 1994; MS074.003.007.00001 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 77. From Reclaiming America conference, 1994.
  - Jonathan Henry, Extraterrestrial life and spiritual experience, 1994; MS074.003.007.00002 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 78. From Reclaiming America Conference, 1994
  - 11/21/84, NPR - ATConsidered, Report on Heritage Foundation, 1984; MS074.003.007.00003 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 79
  - 8/1 Miracle at San Marcos-J. Herrington...8/8 Value free education - Dr. Coulson, MS074.003.007.00004 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 80
  - "Fighting the feminist follies," Susan Hirschman & Kate Walsh O'Beirne, 1994; MS074.003.007.00005 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 81. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - "Luncheon address," Lt. Gov. Mike Huckabee, 1993; MS074.003.007.00006 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape [82]. Labelled 83, but 82 per index. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - What traitors do to you by Patricia Hurley, MS074.003.007.00007 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 83.
  - Howard Hurwitz, 1993-02-13; MS074.003.007.00008 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 84
  - "New York City School Board races," Roy Innis & Mary Cummins, 1993; MS074.003.007.00009 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 85. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - "Breaking the race barrier," Roy Innis, Raul Molina, Armstrong Williams, 1994; MS074.003.007.00010 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 86. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - "Term limits: how to make them work in your state," Rep. Istook, Paul Jacob & St. Rep. Mitchell, 1993; MS074.003.007.00011 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 87. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - [Side 1] Katharyn Iwanowski, sponsored by Eau Claire Chapter, John Birch Society; Side 2 Last of testimony, with questions & answers, ending with songs, MS074.003.007.00012 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 88
  - Bill Jack, A Biblical basis for true authority, 1994; MS074.003.007.00013 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 89. From Reclaiming America Conference, 1994
  - Bill Jack, Creation vs. evolution, 1994; MS074.003.007.00014 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 91. From Reclaiming America Conference, 1994
  - Bill Jack, Torn between two worlds, 1994; MS074.003.007.00015 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 92. From Reclaiming America Conference, 1994
  - "Term limits: restoring a citizens Congress," Paul Jacobs & Dave Mason, 1994; MS074.003.007.00016 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 93. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - "Defending the family: you can make a difference," speaker: Kay James, 1993; MS074.003.007.00017 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 94. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - "Transforming America: from the inside out," speaker: Kay James, 1994; MS074.003.007.00018 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 95. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - Paul Jehle, Christian and humanistic philosophy in education, 1994; MS074.003.007.00019 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 96. From Reclaiming America Conference, 1994
  - Paul Jehle, Reclaiming Christian education, 1994; MS074.003.007.00020 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 97. From Reclaiming America Conference, 1994
  - Why American Christians need to know their Christian heritage, 1994; MS074.003.007.00021 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 98
  - Dee Jepsen, Breaking pornography's chain of abuse, 1994; MS074.003.007.00022 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 99. From Reclaiming America Conference, 1994
  - "Choosing Life," speaker: Gianna Jessen, 1994; MS074.003.007.00023 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 100. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - The Jewish case for Jesus, 1989; MS074.003.007.00024 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 101
  - "The Real Anita Hill & the judicial confirmation process," Jipping, Brock & Berry-Myers, 1993; MS074.003.007.00025 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 102. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - "Supreme Court overview," speaker: Tom Jipping, 1994; MS074.003.007.00026 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 103. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - The new education, Mrs. Dorthy Steinere, MS074.003.007.00027 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 104.
  - "Giving parents a voice: serving on school boards," Stan Jordan & Shelly Uscinski, 1994; MS074.003.007.00028 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 105. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - "Parents seeking a voice in education," Stan Jordan & Mary Cummins, 1993; MS074.003.007.00029 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 106. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - "Strong families & a growing economy," speaker: Jack Kemp, 1993; MS074.003.007.00030 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 107. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993.
  - ACTV: Congressman Jack Kemp, "Reforming America's economic and social agenda", MS074.003.007.00031 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 108
  - Church and state, Dr. D. James Kennedy, MS074.003.007.00032 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 109
  - D. James Kennedy, Spiritual state of the nation, 1994; MS074.003.007.00033 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 110. From Reclaiming America Conference, 1994
  - "True Christian citizenship," speaker: Dr. D. James Kennedy, 1994; MS074.003.007.00034 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 111. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - "Sunday worship service," speaker: Ben Kinchlow, 1993; MS074.003.007.00035 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 112. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - "Gender, sex & politics," Bob Knight, Andrea Sheldon & Connie Marshner, 1993; MS074.003.007.00036 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 113. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - "Outcome Based Education," Gary Kreep & Carolyn Steinke, 1994; MS074.003.007.00037 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 114. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - Media and homosexual issues, Peter LaBarbera, Colorado Family Values, 1994-05-16; MS074.003.007.00038 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 115
  - "The real women's movement," Beverly LaHaye & Phyllis Schlafly, 1993; MS074.003.007.00039 (Box 7)
    IFAS tape 116. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - Beverly LaHaye, The changing values of America, 1994; MS074.003.008.00001 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 117. From Reclaiming America Conference, 1994
  - Side A: CWA tape for election '94 - Tim LaHaye; Side B: Mark Rolfsema speaking at First Parish, (UUA), Concord 3/1/87, 1987 -- 1994; MS074.003.008.00002 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 118
  - "The environment: a pro-family perspective," Dr. Richard Land & Craig Rucker, 1993; MS074.003.008.00003 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 119. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - "Jews and Christians in unity," Speaker: Rabbi Daniel Lapin, 1994; MS074.003.008.00004 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 120. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - #I Jean Hardesty, Skipp Porteous at Olga Mack's 13 Jan; #2 Daniel Levitas at Olga Mack's 13 Jan, 1995; MS074.003.008.00005 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 121
  - #3 at Olga Mack's 13 Jan; #4 at Olga Mack's 13 Jan, 1995; MS074.003.008.00006 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 122
  - "Duty, honor and country," speaker: Sen. Trent Lott, 1994; MS074.003.008.00007 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 123. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - "Outcome Based Education," Peg Luksik & Cheri Yeckel, 1993; MS074.003.008.00008 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 124. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - Religious Liberty Awards banquet addresses by Barry W. Lynn and Elaine Baxter, Iowa Secretary of State, MS074.003.008.00009 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 125. From 46th National Conference on Church and State, Americans United for Separation of Church and State
  - Ralph Marinacci - "The attack against the Fellowship" - excuses - prophecies repeated - more on Oral, MS074.003.008.00010 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 126
  - "The faith of our founders," speaker: Rev. Peter Marshall, 1994; MS074.003.008.00011 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 127. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - "Recovering the American vision," Rev. Peter Marshall, 1992-09-11; MS074.003.008.00012 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 128. From Christian Coalition Leadership School.
  - "Sunday morning worship service," speaker: Rev. Peter Marshall, 1994; MS074.003.008.00013 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 129. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994.
  - Massachusetts law explained, 1994; MS074.003.008.00014 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 130
  - The challenge of the religious right, Rabbi Michael Matuson & Rabbi Eric Yoffie, 1993; MS074.003.008.00015 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 131
  - "Hollywood vs. America," speaker: Michael Medved, 1994; MS074.003.008.00016 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 132. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994.
  - Bill Miller D[?]ville, TX, MS074.003.008.00017 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 133
  - "Health care reform & the family," Sen. Don Nickles & Pat Rooney, 1993; MS074.003.008.00018 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 134. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - "The family and health care reform," Sen. Don Nickles, 1994; MS074.003.008.00019 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 135. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - Christmas - A time to remember, Don Norman and the Branches, MS074.003.008.00020 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 136
  - "God & country banquet," speaker: Oliver North, 1993; MS074.003.008.00021 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 137. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - "The Evangelical-Catholic coalition," Michael Novak & Father Richard Neuhaus, 1994; MS074.003.008.00022 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 138. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994
  - NPR Morning Edition 5/3/93, NYC School Board Race, 1993; MS074.003.008.00023 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 139
  - Madalyn O'Hair, MS074.003.008.00024 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 140
  - The voice of Christmas from the Old Time Gospel Hour, MS074.003.008.00025 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 141
  - Carry me home, a collection of new and old pagan songs, Todd Alan & friends, 1992; MS074.003.008.00026 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 142
  - "School choice & parental rights," Allan Parker & Valerie Barrett, 1993; MS074.003.008.00027 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 143. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1993
  - Gary Parker & Shari Richard, Life before birth, 1994; MS074.003.008.00028 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 144. From Reclaiming America Conference, 1994
  - Gary Parker, Fossils, faith, and the flood, 1994; MS074.003.008.00029 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 145. From Reclaiming America Conference, 1994.
  - Common ground and strategies, Perkins / Linden / Eldredge, Colorado Family Values 5/16/94, 1994; MS074.003.008.00030 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 147.
  - Pete Peters, MS074.003.008.00031 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 148.
  - Tim Philpot, The army of God, 1994; MS074.003.008.00032 (Box 8)
    IFAS tape 149. From Reclaiming America Conference, 1994.